{
    "subject": "resource/The_Paleface_(1922_film)",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "The Paleface",
    "human_readable": "The name of The Paleface (1922 film) is The Paleface.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.923279881477356,
            "question": "What is the name of the 1922 film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8490962386131287,
            "question": "What is another title for the film 'The Paleface'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8178476691246033,
            "question": "In what year was the film 'The Paleface' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7929973006248474,
            "question": "Was 'The Paleface' a popular film upon its release?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7442296743392944,
            "question": "Is 'The Paleface' a fictional story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6833719611167908,
            "question": "Who might have directed or starred in the film 'The Paleface'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6334076523780823,
            "question": "Could you tell me more about the plot of 'The Paleface'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6033884286880493,
            "question": "What genre might the film 'The Paleface' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4685094952583313,
            "question": "Where could I find information about the cast and crew of 'The Paleface'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3725452125072479,
            "question": "Are there any other films from 1922 that you know about?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of The Paleface (1922 film) is The Paleface.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4599_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where could I find information about the cast and crew of 'The Paleface'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4599_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might the film 'The Paleface' belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4599_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you tell me more about the plot of 'The Paleface'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4599_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4599_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4599_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4599_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4599_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4599_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4599_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4599_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4599_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4599_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4599_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states \"1922 film / From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia\" and \"The Paleface (1922)\".  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "To evaluate whether the information in the documents supports the triple \"The name of The Paleface (1922 film) is The Paleface\", I need to search for mentions of the title and year of the film.\n\nAfter searching through the provided context, I found that:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4599/re-ranker-msmarco/16.txt, it is mentioned that \"The Paleface (1922)\".\n* This confirms that The Paleface in question refers to the 1922 film.\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe query correctly states that the title of the 1922 film is \"The Paleface,\" which is supported by the provided documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}